Love. Betrayal. Vengeance
Adulterers is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by H.M. Coakley.
A man who returns home to find his wife cheating on him on their anniversary.
He holds her and her naked and humiliated lover captive at gunpoint
while he decides whether or not he's going to kill them.
The story, inspired by true events, takes place over one day and
is set in New Orleans during a stifling heat wave.
Samuel Deuprey, played by Sean Faris.
Ashley, played by Danielle Savre.
Damien, played by Mehcad Brooks.
Lola, played by Stephanie Charles.
Jasmine, played by Steffinnie Phrommany.
Rebecca Scott, played by Rebecca Reaney.
Adulterers is a 2015 American independent drama film written and directed by H.
It stars Sean Faris, Mehcad Brooks and Danielle Savre in the lead roles.
The film explores themes of adultery, infidelity, hostage, revenge, captive.
The tone is emotional and intense.